This kosher cowboy hasn't got a prayer -- but plenty of laughs.
The Frisco Kid is a adventure, comedy, western film directed by Robert Aldrich.
Rabbi Avram arrives in Philadelphia from Poland en route to San
Francisco where he will be a congregation's new rabbi.
An innocent and inexperienced traveller, he is tricked by con men to pay for the trip to go
west, then they leave him and his belongings scattered along a deserted road.
He is befriended by a stranger, Tommy, who is a bank robber
and have many adventures during their journey.
Avram, played by Gene Wilder.
Tommy, played by Harrison Ford.
Mr. Jones, played by Ramon Bieri.
Chief Gray Cloud, played by Val Bisoglio.
Darryl Diggs, played by George DiCenzo.
Chief Rabbi, played by Leo Fuchs.
The Frisco Kid is a 1979 American Western comedy film directed by Robert Aldrich, starring Gene Wilder as Avram Belinski,
a Polish rabbi who is traveling to San Francisco, and Harrison Ford as a bank robber who befriends him.
The film explores themes of philadelphia,
pennsylvania, bank robber, rabbi, amish.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.